(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-17T21:46:32.224315",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
We're ready to greet the world!
We're voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand-new start
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Cheerfully meeting heart-to-heart!
Waking from a dream, swept up into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue
How will we connect in this new frontier we're journeying through?
Thriving in a scene where no one's ever been
With vibrant colors bursting like stars
Radiant and warm; charged with energy that's carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life, surely
We've gotta take that chance
We're running nonstop; straight to the top
That's right!
We're ready to change the game
A shimmering showcase
Creating a new place where we can shine!
Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves
We're voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand-new stage
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Follow me and we'll turn the page!
Breaking through the doubt, we know we'll figure out a way to clear each towering trial
Sharing all our hopes, we can conquer any challenge with a smile!
We'll link our hearts as we search across the globe
Knowing, no matter where we are, no matter how far, we can be stars, let's go!
I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly
Playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see
Making them reality!
Take my hand and reach for the screen
All we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls, all fulfilled in the world we build!
We're ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways, discovering highways to everywhere!
Step by step, gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation, a dream unfurls
Let's make friends, making a moment of history, joyfully!
Follow me, we'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We'll carry on, starting now, setting hearts in motion
Connecting all of the world!
We're ready to greet the world, we're voyaging forward
With courage to run toward a brand new start
Let's go live, bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Cheerfully meeting heart to heart
Waking from a dream, swept up into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue
How will we connect in this new frontier we're journeying through?
Thriving in a scene where no one's ever been
With vibrant colors bursting like stars
Radiant and warm; charged with energy that's carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life, surely
We've gotta take that chance, we're running nonstop
Straight to the top, that's right!
We're ready to change the game, a shimmering showcase
Creating a new place where we can shine
Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves, we're voyaging forward
With courage to run towards a brand new stage
Let's go live, bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Follow me, and we'll turn the page
Breaking through the doubt, we know we'll figure out
A way to clear each towering trial
Sharing all our hopes, we can conquer any challenge with a smile
We'll link our hearts and we search across the globe, knowing
No matter where we are, no matter how far
We can be stars, let's go!
I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly
Playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see
Making them reality
Take my hand and reach for the screen
All we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls, all fulfilled in the world we build
We're ready to seize the day, traversing the pathways
Discovering highways to everywhere
Step by step, gathering stories that we can share
Get ready to lead the way with each generation
A shining sensation, a dream unfurls
Let's make friends, making a moment of history joyfully
Follow me, we'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues
We'll carry on starting now, setting hearts in motion
Connecting all of the world!
We're ready to greet the world, we're voyaging forward
With courage to run toward a brand new start
Let's go live, bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Cheerfully meeting heart to heart
Waking from a dream, swept up into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue
How will we connect in this new frontier we're journeying through?
Thriving in a scene where no one's ever been
With vibrant colors bursting like stars
Radiant and warm; charged with energy that's carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life, surely
We've gotta take that chance, we're running nonstop
Straight to the top, that's right!
We're ready to change the game, a shimmering showcase
Creating a new place where we can shine
Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves, we're voyaging forward
With courage to run towards a brand new stage
Let's go live, bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Follow me, and we'll turn the page
Breaking through the doubt, we know we'll figure out
A way to clear each towering trial
Sharing all our hopes, we can conquer any challenge with a smile
We'll link our hearts and we search across the globe, knowing
No matter where we are, no matter how far
We can be stars, let's go!
I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly
Playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see
Making them reality
Take my hand and reach for the screen
All we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls, all fulfilled in the world we build
We're ready to seize the day, traversing the pathways
Discovering highways to everywhere
Step by step, gathering stories that we can share
Get ready to lead the way with each generation
A shining sensation, a dream unfurls
Let's make friends, making a moment of history joyfully
Follow me...
We're ready to greet the world!
We're voyaging forward with courage
To run toward a brand-new start
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Cheerfully meeting heart-to-heart!
Waking from a dream, swept up into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue
How will we connect in this
New frontier we're journeying through?
Thriving in a scene where no one's ever been
With vibrant colors bursting like stars
Radiant and warm
Charged with energy that's carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life, surely
We've gotta take that chance
We're running nonstop, straight to the top
That's right!
We're ready to change the game
A shimmering showcase
Creating a new place where we can shine!
Day by day (yeah!)
Sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves
We're voyaging forward with courage
To run toward a brand-new stage
Let's go live! (yeah!)
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Follow me and we'll turn the page!
Breaking through the doubt, we know
We'll figure out a way to clear each towering trial
Sharing all our hopes
We can conquer any challenge with a smile!
We'll link our hearts as we search across the globe
Knowing, no matter where we are, no matter how far
We can be stars, let's go!
I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly
Playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see
Making them reality!
Take my hand and reach for the screen
All we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls
All fulfilled in the world we build!
We're ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways
Discovering highways to everywhere!
Step by step (yeah!)
Gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation
A dream unfurls
Let's make friends (yeah!)
Making a moment of history, joyfully!
Follow me, we'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We'll carry on, starting now, setting hearts in motion
Connecting all of the world!
They'll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We'll carry on, starting now, setting hearts in motion
Connecting all of the world!
ヴァイスシュヴァルツ
Weiß Schwarz
hololive production is back
with another big round-up,
expanding Weiß Schwarz!
hololive production Vol. 2 booster pack
coming soon!
BUSHIROAD
I know, I know.
You guys have been dying for a new PC, right?
We're ready to greet the world!
We're voyaging forward with courage
To run toward a brand-new start
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly, cheerfully meeting heart-to-heart!
Waking from a dream, swept up into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue—
How will we connect in this
new frontier we’re journeying through?
Thriving in a scene where no one’s ever been
with vibrant colors bursting like stars—
Radiant and warm; charged with energy
that’s carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life
Surely
We've gotta take that chance
We’re running nonstop; straight to the top, that’s right!
We’re ready to change the game
A shimmering showcase
Creating a new place where we can shine!
Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves
We’re voyaging forward with courage
To run toward a brand-new stage
Let’s go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Follow me and we’ll turn the page!
Breaking through the doubt, we know
We’ll figure out a way to clear each towering trial;
Sharing all our hopes,
We can conquer any challenge with a smile!
We’ll link our hearts as we search across the globe
Knowing
No matter where we are, no matter how far
We can be stars
Let’s go!
I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly,
Playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see
Making them reality!
Take my hand and reach for the screen
All we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls, all fulfilled in the world we build!
We’re ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways,
Discovering highways to everywhere!
Step by step, gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation;
A dream unfurls —
Let’s make friends,
Making a moment of history joyfully!
Follow me; we’ll connect the world!
They’ll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We’ll carry on starting now; setting hearts in motion —
Connecting all of the world!
We're ready to greet the world!
We're voyaging forward with courage
To run toward a brand-new start
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly, cheerfully meeting heart-to-heart!
Waking from a dream, swept up into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue—
How will we connect in this
new frontier we’re journeying through?
Thriving in a scene where no one’s ever been
with vibrant colors bursting like stars—
Radiant and warm; charged with energy
that’s carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life
Surely
We've gotta take that chance
We’re running nonstop; straight to the top, that’s right!
We’re ready to change the game
A shimmering showcase
Creating a new place where we can shine!
Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves
We’re voyaging forward with courage
To run toward a brand-new stage
Let’s go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Follow me and we’ll turn the page!
Breaking through the doubt, we know
We’ll figure out a way to clear each towering trial;
Sharing all our hopes,
We can conquer any challenge with a smile!
We’ll link our hearts as we search across the globe
Knowing
No matter where we are, no matter how far
We can be stars
Let’s go!
I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly,
Playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see
Making them reality!
Take my hand and reach for the screen
All we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls, all fulfilled in the world we build!
We’re ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways,
Discovering highways to everywhere!
Step by step, gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation;
A dream unfurls —
Let’s make friends,
Making a moment of history joyfully!
Follow me; we’ll connect the world!
They’ll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We’ll carry on starting now; setting hearts in motion —
Connecting all of the world!
We're ready to greet the world!
We're voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand-new start
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Cheerful meeting heart to heart!
Waking from a dream, swept up into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue—
How will we connect in this new frontier we're journeying through?
Thriving in a scene where no one's ever been
With vibrant colors bursting like stars—
Radiant and warm; charged with energy that's carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life, surely
We've gotta take that chance
We're running nonstop; straight to the top
That's right!
We're ready to change the game
A shimmering showcase
Creating a new place where we can shine!
Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves
We're voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand-new stage
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Follow me and we'll turn the page!
Breaking through the doubt, we know we'll figure out a way to clear each towering trial;
Sharing all our hopes, we can conquer any challenge with a smile!
We'll link our hearts as we search across the globe
Knowing, no matter where we are, no matter how far
We can be stars
Let's go!
I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly,
Playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see
Making them reality!
Take my hand and reach for the screen
All we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls,
All fulfilled in the world we build!
We're ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways, discovering highways to everywhere!
Step by step, gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation;
A dream unfurls—
Let's make friends,
Making a moment of history joyfully!
Follow me; we'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We'll carry on starting now; setting hearts in motion—
Connecting all of the world!
We're ready to greet the world!
We're voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand-new start
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Cheerful meeting heart to heart!
Waking from a dream, swept up into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue—
How will we connect in this new frontier we're journeying through?
Thriving in a scene where no one's ever been
With vibrant colors bursting like stars—
Radiant and warm; charged with energy that's carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life, surely
We've gotta take that chance
We're running nonstop; straight to the top
That's right!
We're ready to change the game
A shimmering showcase
Creating a new place where we can shine!
Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves
We're voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand-new stage
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Follow me and we'll turn the page!
Breaking through the doubt, we know we'll figure out a way to clear each towering trial;
Sharing all our hopes, we can conquer any challenge with a smile!
We'll link our hearts as we search across the globe
Knowing, no matter where we are, no matter how far
We can be stars
Let's go!
I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly,
Playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see
Making them reality!
Take my hand and reach for the screen
All we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls,
All fulfilled in the world we build!
We're ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways, discovering highways to everywhere!
Step by step, gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation;
A dream unfurls—
Let's make friends,
Making a moment of history joyfully!
Follow me; we'll connect the world!
I know, I know, you guys have been dying for one of these, right?
We're ready to greet the world!
We're voyaging forward with courage
To run toward a brand-new start
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Cheerful meeting heart to heart!
Waking from a dream, swept up into a stream
I make a wish and wait for my cue
How will we connect in this
New frontier we're journeying through?
Thriving in a scene where no one's ever been
With vibrant colors bursting like stars
Radiant and warm; charged with energy
That's carried us this far
Each new debut brings a miracle to life
Surely
We've gotta take that chance
We're running nonstop; straight to the top
That's right!
We're ready to change the game
A shimmering showcase
Creating a new place where we can shine!
Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
Get ready to cross the waves
We're voyaging forward with courage
To run toward a brand-new stage
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Follow me and we'll turn the page!
Breaking through the doubt, we know
We'll figure out a way to clear each towering trial;
Sharing all our hopes,
We can conquer any challenge with a smile!
We'll link our hearts as we search across the globe
Knowing
No matter where we are, no matter how far
We can be stars
Let's go!
I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly,
Playing out a grand story
Share the futures that we can see
Making them reality!
Take my hand and reach for the screen
All we need are glittering dreams
Our hearts and souls,
All fulfilled in the world we build!
We're ready to seize the day
Traversing the pathways,
Discovering highways to everywhere!
Step by step, gathering stories that we can share!
Get ready to lead the way
With each generation, a shining sensation;
A dream unfurls —
Let's make friends,
Making a moment of history joyfully!
Follow me; we'll connect the world!
They'll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans
Our legend grows and continues!
We'll carry on starting now; setting hearts in motion —
Connecting all of the world!
Welcome to YouTube Theater.
Your safety is our number one priority.
In the event that it becomes necessary
to evacuate YouTube Theater,
please follow these guidelines to walk calmly
out and away from the facility.
Those exiting the floor seats proceed
to the nearest safe stairwell on either side of the stage.
Continue up the stairs until
you get to an exterior exit.
Once outside, please continue
to walk away from the facility.
Those seated in orchestra sections 101 through 105, walk up the aisles and out onto the concourse.
Those in the box and club areas, exit out of your box or the club onto the concourse.
Follow directions of YouTube staff who will be available to guide you to the nearest safe exit.
If you're seated on the plaza level sections, walk up the aisles, turn left or right, and proceed out the door.
Those on the balcony level, walk up the aisles onto the concourse, turn left or right, and continue down the nearest safe stairway to the ground level concourse and out the door.
Once outside, please continue to walk away from the facility.
Elevators will not be in service during an emergency evacuation.
YouTube theater staff will be available to guide and assist you.
For those who are unable to use stairs, YouTube theater staff will be available to assist you via an evacuation chair.
This has been the evacuation plan for YouTube theater.
Thank you for being prepared ahead of time to respond calmly in an emergency.
Enjoy the event.
We're ready to greet the world!
We're voyaging forward with courage
To run toward a brand-new start
Let's go live!
Bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
Cheerfully meeting heart-to-heart!
Thank you for coming to hololive English first concert, Connect the World,
supported by Bushiroad, up at the YouTube Theater here in Inglewood, California today!
This is Friend A, also known as A-chan.
The time has finally come.
Today, we celebrate the accomplishments of the girls of hololive English,
and take another step towards their bright future. Are you ready to become part of hololive English history?
All right! Let's go! Connect the World!
おなじみの日々を見ていたい
I want to watch those familiar days,
あの夢手にしたい
and make that dream my own.
それぞれ誓った心で走れよ
Run with the heart each of us swore upon!
ぞっと見ても真っ赤な場所に芽生えてた
Even taking a closer look, it sprouted in a bright red place
ほんの小さな希望に
into the tiniest hope.
この瞳見つめられた不安で揺れる心も
Even the heart trembling with anxiety when stared into by these eyes
うまく宙に結んで
can skillfully tie it into the air,
ほんの小さな勇気をふりしぼっていたよ
and muster up even the smallest bit of courage.
諦めの文字手にして進む苦しい時も
Even in painful times when we push forward carrying resignation,
もうあたしは一人じゃないから
I'm no longer alone anymore, so—
宝物夢追いかけたい ワクワクとまらない
I want to chase my treasured dream, excitement won't stop!
その外を越えてく 世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that goes beyond that outer edge.
アクセスしてみたい 後悔なんてさせない
I want to try accessing it, I won't let you have any regrets.
それぞれ誓った心で走れよ
Run with the heart each of us swore upon!
星空に輝くまぶしい思いは見たことのない光を
The dazzling feelings shining in the starry night sky
リアルに見届けるよ
will witness a light like never before in reality!
いつも聞こえるエールはここにキャプチャして
Capture the cheers we always hear right here,
また新しい光を探したくなるよ
and you'll want to search for a brand new light once more.
君の笑顔は保存して進む
Saving your smile as we press forward,
悲しいときに磨かすよ
we'll polish it up in times of sorrow.
力から渇くから
From strength to thirst,
胸を張って夢を追いかけたい
puffing out our chests, we want to chase our dreams.
奇跡のストーリー一緒に作ろう
Let's create a miraculous story together!
終わらない夢を一人じゃ欠かせない
We can never leave anyone behind on this endless dream.
愛が待ったこの世界 それぞれ誓った心で
Love awaits in this world, with hearts each of us swore upon,
色とりどれ
colorful and bright!
悲しいときも寂しいときも信じ合えるものが
Even when we're sad or lonely, if there's something we share,
ある お互いずにこの鼓動を
it exists. Let's keep this beat going without losing each other—
新しく続けたい
wanting to continue anew,
終わらない世界に飛び出すよ
leaping out into an endless world!
憧れの舞台に立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage I've longed for,
険しく輝きたい
shining brightly through the steep climb.
時に涙して
Sometimes shedding tears,
また笑い合いたい
and laughing together once more.
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future,
あの夢手に入れたい
and grasp that dream in my hands.
踏み出すぞ 奇跡の一歩を
Taking that miraculous first step forward!
行き交い出して 夢追いかけたい
Crossing paths, I want to chase my dreams.
ワクワクと止まらない 想像を超えてゆく
Excitement never stops, surpassing imagination.
想像を超えてゆく
Surpassing imagination,
世界に見せてあげる
I'll show it to the world!
アクセプトしてみたい
I want to try accepting it.
後悔なんてここにない
There's no room for regrets here.
それぞれ誓った心で
With the hearts we've each sworn upon,
つくるわ
we will create it!
Hello, everyone!
What's up, everybody? What's up, Los Angeles?
We're finally here, Kiara!
Yeah, yes! Hug me, sister!
Isn't that amazing?
That's amazing! That's beautiful!
So cool.
Hi everybody! Calm down, calm down.
Hololive English's first concert ever, Connect the World, has finally begun!
It's begun, everybody! Let me hear you cheer!
Come on, let me hear your voices! Hey, you did it, you did it!
The first MC part, the first MC is us, Takamori, Kiwawa, Kuwasyupi, from Myth!
Hello! Hey, hey, hey, hey, guys! Thank you, thank you!
So the first song was the fan favorite shiny smiley story!
She's excited, we started off with a banger though, right everyone?
Yeah, yeah. Well, this is also the first time we've ever had so many whole life English fans here together in one place!
Yeah, yeah. Well, this is also the first time we've ever had so many Hololive English fans here together in one place!
Also on the stream too, yeah? Are you guys watching?
All right, I already asked them to do this before, but I want them to do it again. Everyone at the venue, raise your voice, shout as hard as you can!
All right, I already asked them to do this before, but I want them to do it again. Everyone at the venue, raise your voices as loud as you can!
Second floor, second floor!
I want to hear second floor, third floor!
First floor! Go, first floor! Come on!
So loud! So loud!
Thank you!
Yeah, I think that that is sufficient. All right, all right, chill, chill, chill, chill, chill.
What? What do you want? I always do this like everywhere. You guys know what I want to do.
What? What do you want? I always do this everywhere. You guys know what I want to do.
Do you guys know what I want to do? Oh god, I know what she wants to do. Yes. Yes. I want to do the wave.
Can we do the wave?
Don't you think we already hyped them up enough?
No! It's exciting!
I don't even know if we have time. Start on a wave. Yes. All right, fine, let's do it.
Okay, people go over here, and when we reach your point, you raise your arms. You can even stand up if you want.
Yeah. Okay. Are you ready?
Here we go. Get ready. Three, two, one.
Come on! Raise them up! Raise them up!
Very nice, and!
Back! We're bringing it back, we're bringing it back!
Wonderful, wonderful!
Okay, no more, no more wave. Applause.
It's done. It's done.
Thank you. Thanks, guys. I think that they're sufficiently hyped up.
Everybody's real excited, yeah? Don't answer that. You don't need to scream anymore.
Everybody's really excited, yeah? Don't answer that. You don't need to scream anymore.
You don't. You're going to lose the voices by the end of the concert.
You don't. You're going to lose your voices by the end of the concert.
You're right. No, we should refrain from hyping them up anymore.
Well, yeah. So we're going to kick off the solo songs actually from now on. Gonna hear a lot of EN member solo, and we'll give it our best.
Well, yeah. So we're going to kick off the solo songs actually from now on. We're going to hear a lot of EN member solos, and we'll give it our best.
So please cheer for us! All right, very nice. Thank you.
It's only just begun.
We ain't gonna stop either, and I have confidence that you guys won't either. You guys will keep the energy going all the way to the end, okay?
Don't stop!
All right, very nice.
So together, three, two, one, let's go!
Connect the world!
Los Angeles! Are you ready?!
Hey! どんな壁も 悠々越えて
Hey! Easily crossing over any wall,
未知なる渦へ 吸い込まれていく
getting sucked into an unknown vortex.
地球もそろそろ まわり疲れて飽きちゃう
Earth is getting tired of spinning and bored soon.
不甲斐ないぜ どこまで転がる
How pathetic, how far will it keep rolling?
輪廻転生 繰り返される営み
Reincarnation, repeated activities of life,
喧騒混ざりこんで 召し上がれ
mixed with commotion, come and feast on it.
悪意が僕を 三里落してやまない
Malice drops me three millimeters endlessly.
ガラクタのクズは 入ったら綺麗ね
Once you gather the junk, it looks so pretty.
罪の重さで こんばん人参
With the weight of sin, good evening carrot.
愛したいな 生きたいな 壊したいな やめたいな
I want to love, live, break, and quit
世界が僕らを嫌うなら
if the world hates us.
左胸で踊り狂う
Dancing wildly in my left chest,
素っ気無いまわりがしがみついて高ぶる
indifferent surroundings cling and get excited.
赤い飯して 踊けたわごと
Eating red rice, foolish nonsense,
残酷は自身のずらして
shifting cruelty away from myself.
揺れながらもてあそんで
Swaying and playing around,
弱者はいじめて 踏みつけて
bullying the weak and stepping on them.
サイコサイコ
Psycho, psycho.
自分してよう 刈ってはめじゃくちゃ
Be yourself, mowing everything down into a mess,
刺してほら その細い針
stab, look, that thin needle.
不確かな 頼りなさ
Uncertain and unreliable,
泣きそうでも 中心向けでしょ
even if you look like you're crying, aim for the center.
これが遅きで
Is this too late?
孤独に染まるには
To be dyed in loneliness,
情愛的な恋
affectionate love,
僕はどこまで行けるのか
how far can I go?
醜いな 汚いな 美しいな 素晴らしいな
Ugly, filthy, beautiful, wonderful,
時代よ僕を受け止めて
era, please accept me.
Let me hear you scream!
愛したいな 生きたいな 壊したいな やめたいな
I want to love, live, break, and quit
世界が僕らを嫌うなら
if the world hates us.
左胸で踊り狂う
Dancing wildly in my left chest,
素っ気無いまわりがしがみついて高ぶる
indifferent surroundings cling and get excited.
赤い飯して 踊けたわごと
Eating red rice, foolish nonsense,
残虐は自身のずらして
shifting cruelty away from myself.
揺れながらもてあそんで
Swaying and playing around,
弱者はいじめて 踏みつけて
bullying the weak and stepping on them.
サイコサイコ
Psycho, psycho.
自分してよう 刈ってはめじゃくちゃ
Be yourself, mowing everything down into a mess,
刺してほら その細い針
stab, look, that thin needle.
不確かな 頼りなさ
Uncertain and unreliable,
泣きそうでも 中心向けでしょ
even if you look like you're crying, aim for the center.
僕がいつか飽きるまで
Until I get bored someday,
ただ遊ぼう
let's just play.
Let me hear you scream!
愛したいな 生きたいな 壊したいな やめたいな
I want to love, live, break, and quit
世界が僕らを嫌うなら
if the world hates us.
左胸で踊り狂う
Dancing wildly in my left chest,
素っ気無いまわりがしがみついて高ぶる
indifferent surroundings cling and get excited.
赤い飯して 踊けたわごと
Eating red rice, foolish nonsense,
残虐は自身のずらして
shifting cruelty away from myself.
揺れながらもてあそんで
Swaying and playing around,
弱者はいじめて 踏みつけて
bullying the weak and stepping on them.
サイコサイコ
Psycho, psycho.
Come on, sing it!
愛したいな 生きたいな 壊したいな やめたいな
I want to love, live, break, and quit
世界が僕らを嫌うなら
if the world hates us.
That's right, I'm not just a detective! I'm a time traveler! Let's go, Ame!
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
Waku waku, how should I know
why it seems when you're here with me
the clock won't stop spinning?
Wapu wapu wapu wapu
Doki doki, hearts beat faster
Tomodachi, friends forever
it's clear to see that this mystery
was solved immediately
Jiku no yugami
When we first met, I wonder what you'd think of me
the image was set, it was a perfect narrative
but as time went by, I forgot to hide
the laughs that came so naturally
Through lows and highs, I'd wonder why
I ever thought you would leave
Now no matter where or when we are
I know it's you I can count on
Magical, mythical
Nothing can stop us now!
Let's go!
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
Waku waku, how should I know
why it seems when you're here with me
the clock won't stop spinning?
Wapu wapu wapu wapu
Doki doki, hearts beat faster
Tomodachi, friends forever
That's right, I'm not just a detective ! !
That's right, I'm not just a detective!!
I'm a time traveler !
I'm a time traveler!
Watch this !
Watch this!
It's been so long
Since they laughed so hard I cried
Now you came along
It happens almost every time that I hear your voice
And left no choice 'cause you let you know
What you need to mean, spiraling
Time skipping through treasured
Memories, now no matter where
Or when we're from, our friendship
Fell elementary, case closed
Now you know
Nothing can stop us now
Let's go !
Let's go!
Chikutaku, where'd the time go ?
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
Waku waku, how should I know
Why it seems when you're here with me
The clock won't stop spinning, wapu wapu wapu wapu
Doki doki, hearts beat faster, tomodachi
Friends forever, it's clear to see that this mystery
Was solved immediately, chiku no yugami
Though each day, we're older
What the future holds is not, not, not for us to know yet
Gone, gone, gone before we know it
So let's solve the question, we can make each second
Chikutaku last forever
Waku waku, it's now or never !
Waku waku, it's now or never!
Chikutaku, where'd the time go ?
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
Waku waku, how should I know
Why it seems when you're here with me
The clock won't stop spinning, wapu wapu wapu wapu
Doki doki, hearts beat faster, tomodachi
Friends forever, it's clear to see that this mystery
Was solved immediately, chiku no yugami
Chikutaku, where'd the time go ?
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
Waku waku, how should I know
Why it seems when you're here with me
The clock won't stop spinning, wapu wapu wapu wapu
Doki doki, hearts beat faster, tomodachi
Friends forever, it's clear to see that this mystery
Was solved immediately, chiku no yugami
That's right, I'm not just a detective ! !
That's right, I'm not just a detective!!
I'm a time traveler !
I'm a time traveler!
Look at this !
Look at this!
We're here! Hello! Hello!
Yay! Haha! Yay!
Yay! Hi everyone! Hi Amelia! Hi everyone!
Ame! Yeah!
Hey ChikuTaku!
Yeah! How'd you like my ChikuTaku?
Oh, she's so cute!
Ame, you're so cute.
Now stop, don't.
Stay over there. Stay on that side. It's fine. It's fine.
The solo parts have begun.
Yeah. Oh, and Bae's dancing was so good.
She's always so good at dancing.
She's such a good dancer.
Right, and thanks all of you guys who support us so we can perform live here.
So thank you!
Welcome to YouTube Theater!
I know.
Have you ever been here before?
I know. It's so fun. I've never been here.
Look at them up there.
Ah, you, you, I see you.
I see you, you, and you.
I know there's one right there.
I know. Can you... it's almost... it's almost three years since we debuted.
Like, did you ever imagine standing in YouTube Theater, like performing like that?
I couldn't imagine it being like this.
No, it's crazy. It's so cool. This place is huge. I know.
Okay, there's one thing I really, really wanted to try.
One thing?
Are you guys ready?
I say "wa".
You say "wa"!
Wa!
Was that pretty good? Yeah, it's pretty loud.
It's like... I don't know, it's so unreal hearing you guys.
It kind of sounded like one side was louder than the other.
Oh, you're sure?
Yeah, I think we have to test it.
We have to test it.
Yeah, you guys can cheer or say "wa", whatever you want.
Yeah, no cursing.
Which side do you choose?
This side?
I picked this side.
Okay, I get this side!
You want to go first? I'll go first.
All right, my side, I'm a team. Team Ame!
Okay, you can count to three, okay?
One, two, three!
Woo, let's go!
I don't know, they seemed a little quiet.
No, not at all.
Well, this side, you guys know what's up, right? You guys are ready. You're born for this!
せーの！ちゅっ！
Ready? Chuu!
We can hear you!
All right, we'll just say it was a tie.
Okay, it was a tie, you know? I'm all for peace.
Yeah.
Well, we do have an important announcement for those of you watching the livestream. Hello, live viewers on YouTube!
Well, unfortunately the YouTube sneak peek ends here. Get out of here!
But the solo parts will continue.
And who do you guys think is next?
Who's next?
What was that?
Who's that?
Do we smell sea urchin?
Is that stinky? Stinky fish?
Goodbye! Goodbye! Good night!
So, if you'd like to continue watching, please buy the streaming ticket
on one of the available streaming platforms.
You know, I'm sure there are some Japanese fans watching too, so could you please explain to them in Japanese?
Ah!
Hold on, let me pull up my Nihongo jouzu card.
え, この放送を見ている日本の皆さん!
To everyone in Japan watching this broadcast!
えっと, 残念ですが, YouTubeのちらみせはここで終了になります.
Um, unfortunately, the YouTube preview ends right here.
ソロパートはこれからも続きますので, ぜひぜひ, あの, ストリームサイトで見てください!
The solo parts will continue from here on, so please, please watch on the streaming site!
次はごちゃんだです!
Next is Gura-chan!
じゃあ, あの, 各プラットフォームのあの, ライブ視聴チケットを買って, 見ててくださいね!
So, um, please buy a live streaming ticket on each platform and watch!
いや, 日本語難しいね.
Man, Japanese is hard.
Oh, thank you. Next to the A-ship!
We hope you all continue to enjoy Connect the World!
Okay, since we're here live, we can do this live.
You guys can join us in saying, if we say "se-no", you're going to say "Connect the World with us", okay?
Okay.
You say "se-no".
Okay, okay.
せーの! Connect the World!
Ready? Connect the World!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended. Thank you for watching!